<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>homepage on craneppeakare</title>
    <link>https://craneppeakare.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in homepage on craneppeakare</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 14:08:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://craneppeakare.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I Built a Scrabble Trainer to Beat My Friends</title>
      <link>https://craneppeakare.github.io/projects/i-built-a-scrabble-trainer-to-beat-my-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 14:08:57 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://craneppeakare.github.io/projects/i-built-a-scrabble-trainer-to-beat-my-friends/</guid>
      <description>So me and my close friends love playing Discord&amp;rsquo;s in-client game Letter League, which is based off of the popular word game Scrabble. We&amp;rsquo;d play for hours at a time and one of our friends in particular, we will call him &amp;ldquo;Nigel&amp;rdquo;, tends to consistently win somewhat often. And I&amp;rsquo;m an ultra competitive person so I built a trainer program to help me find 7 letter words, known as &amp;ldquo;bingos&amp;rdquo; in scabble, and go on the training arc of my life and beat him to the ground.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporting Bug Template</title>
      <link>https://craneppeakare.github.io/notes/reporting-bug-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 23:07:19 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://craneppeakare.github.io/notes/reporting-bug-template/</guid>
      <description>This holds a basic tempplate and guide for building bug reports that can be filled out quickly.&#xA;Title: Severity: Informational: no real current security impact Low: Business impact is low Medium: Potential to cause harm to users but not revealing data High: Potential to reveal customer data or aids in exploitation of other vulnerabilities Critical: High risk of personal/confidential data exposure, general system compromise, and other severe impacts to business Description: Short description of said vulnerability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Networking</title>
      <link>https://craneppeakare.github.io/notes/networking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 18:55:53 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://craneppeakare.github.io/notes/networking/</guid>
      <description>Tools ping traceroute whois dig (manually query recursive DNS servers of our choice for information about domains) TCP/IP Model Abstraction model for understanding the different stages of networking. Contains 7 layers of abstraction, each on built on top of the next.&#xA;Layer 5: Application + ---------- + ------------- + | | | | L5 | Data (Data) | | Header | | | | | + ---------- + ------------- + Tries to establish a connection to the recieving computer across a network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rubik&#39;s Cube: An Icon of Pop Culture and Solvable Puzzle for Everyone (With Visuals)</title>
      <link>https://craneppeakare.github.io/hobbies/rubiks-cube-how-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 17:08:57 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://craneppeakare.github.io/hobbies/rubiks-cube-how-to/</guid>
      <description>The Rubik&amp;rsquo;s Cube, invented in 1974 by Ernő Rubik, is a icon of pop culture appearing in major shows such as The Big Bang Theory, The Simpsons, various Spiderman movies, and even in Rick and Morty. Although pop culture loves to portray the puzzle as if only geniuses can solve the cube, in reality anyone can learn to solve one is as little as 5 minutes. And if you invest a little bit more time you can gain the skills to solve it in under 60 seconds and impress all your friends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Summary] Ultralearning by Scott H. Young</title>
      <link>https://craneppeakare.github.io/books/ultralearningsummary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 19:37:45 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://craneppeakare.github.io/books/ultralearningsummary/</guid>
      <description>This is a no-bullshit summary of the book &amp;ldquo;Ultralearning&amp;rdquo; by Scott H. Young. Before getting to the 9 principles of what makes an effective Ultralearner, Schott H. Young prefaces by explaining the manic-level obbession that many ultralearners exhibit to their chosen skill. They obsess over every tiny efficiency and detail, and while this degree of obsession may be difficult to achieve for a skill meant just as a simple hobby or to promote skills beneficial to your work force, learning their principles can help you become a more effective learning for anything you may wish to pursue in your life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating an Infinite Scroller Minesweeper App</title>
      <link>https://craneppeakare.github.io/projects/infinite-minesweeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:55:30 -0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://craneppeakare.github.io/projects/infinite-minesweeper/</guid>
      <description>Right away I knew it would be a great concept however, I was by no means a game dev. Sure, I&amp;rsquo;ve dabbled here in there making basic platformers and getting used to the basic functions of a game through engines like Godot and Pygame. I sure as hell didn&amp;rsquo;t know anything about mobile game dev. So how did I do it?&#xA;It all started when I had the idea to combine the typical infinite scroller style mobile games with an age old classic, Minesweeper, which to my knowledge hadn&amp;rsquo;t been done yet before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://craneppeakare.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://craneppeakare.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.&#xA;Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:&#xA;https://github.com/yuin/goldmark https://github.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
