<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on craneppeakare</title>
    <link>https://craneppeakare.github.io/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on craneppeakare</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 19:37:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://craneppeakare.github.io/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[Review] Ultralearning by Scott H. Young</title>
      <link>https://craneppeakare.github.io/books/ultralearningreview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 19:37:45 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://craneppeakare.github.io/books/ultralearningreview/</guid>
      <description>Finally my long awaited review of the book &amp;ldquo;Ultralearning&amp;rdquo; by Scott H. Young. I have been putting this off for far too long. This will not be a summary of the book as I have already done so in another post which you can find here. As someone who loves constantly learning new hobbies I thought this book would be right up my alley for leveling up my abilities.&#xA;The book opens itself well by defining the demographic who would benefit the most from this book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Summary] Ultralearning by Scott H. Young</title>
      <link>https://craneppeakare.github.io/books/ultralearningsummary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 19:37:45 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://craneppeakare.github.io/books/ultralearningsummary/</guid>
      <description>This is a no-bullshit summary of the book &amp;ldquo;Ultralearning&amp;rdquo; by Scott H. Young. Before getting to the 9 principles of what makes an effective Ultralearner, Schott H. Young prefaces by explaining the manic-level obbession that many ultralearners exhibit to their chosen skill. They obsess over every tiny efficiency and detail, and while this degree of obsession may be difficult to achieve for a skill meant just as a simple hobby or to promote skills beneficial to your work force, learning their principles can help you become a more effective learning for anything you may wish to pursue in your life.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
